Finding Aid for the June Wayne Papers LSC.0562
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 9: Photographs, 1911-2011
  - Oversize -- Dorothy Series Contact Sheets, circa 1977 (Box 154, Folder 1)
    14 16 x 20" contact sheets, 1 12.5 x 20" contact sheet, 1 8 x 10" contact sheet, 35mm negative prints attached to each contact sheet.
    Contact sheets from photographs Wayne took of Dorothy Kline's lingerie and shoes. Some of the photographs were used to make photolithography zinc plates for the prints in the Dorothy series.
  - Oversize -- Dorothy Series Prints, circa 1977 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    12 16 x 20" photographs.
    Photographs are of Dorothy Kline's lingerie and shoes. Some of these were used to create photolithography zinc plates.
- Series 10: Audiovisual Materials, 1950-2011
  This series is organized into five subseries by format: Reel-to-Reel Audio; Cassettes; Compact Discs; Films; and Documentation. Within each subseries, material is arranged chronologically.
  The objects in this series are recordings either made by or about June Wayne or the Tamarind Workshop.
  - Subseries 1: Reel-to-Reel Audio, 1953-1981
    This subseries includes audio recordings of radio broadcasts, interviews, and seminar and symposia presentations. Included are recordings of the discussion series, You and Modern Art, organized by Wayne with art critic, Jules Langsner, as well as Wayne's Joan of Art seminar series.
    - June Wayne interviewed by Gunter Troche (28 minutes), 1958 (Box 118, Folder 1)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 7 1/2 IPS. Gunter Troche was director of Achenbach Foundation. The reel has defects in the recording from 245-253 and was dubbed for Pat Gilmour in 1994.
    - June Wayne interviewed by John Zee (26 minutes) -- Talk of New York Program, New York City, 1964 October 16 (Box 118, Folder 2)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 7 1/2 IPS in cardboard box. Wayne being interviewed about Tamarind Workshop.
    - June Wayne interviewed by John Zee (26 minutes) -- Talk of New York Program, New York City (duplicate), 1964 October 16 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - June Wayne speech at California State University at Fullerton, 1964 October (Box 118, Folder 4)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 3 3/4 IPS in cardboard box. Wayne's speech is about lithography and Tamarind Workshop.
    - June Wayne interviewed by Fred Anderson -- Kaleidoscope KNX Los Angeles, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 5)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 7 1/2 IPS in cardboard box. Also interviewed on the episode are Brach, Gardener, Powell, and Allen.
    - June Wayne interviewed by Edith Walton -- NBC, 1964 October 15 (Box 118, Folder 6)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel.
    - June Wayne on Livre de Luxe (22 minutes), 1965 September 2 (Box 118, Folder 7)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 3 3/4 IPS in cardboard box.
    - June Wayne speaking about the history of Tamarind, 1967 February (Box 118, Folder 8)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 3 3/4 IPS in cardboard box. Side 1 is June Wayne speaking about the history and objectives of Tamarind Workshop, and side 2 is a continuation of the history of Tamarind Workshop with the voice of William Gropper at the end. Taped on February 3 and 24.
    - June Wayne at Art Symposium, Florida State University (part 1), 1967 February 18 (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - June Wayne at Art Symposium, Florida State University (part 2), 1967 February 18 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - June Wayne at University of California, Los Angeles, 1967 February 27 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Mario Avati talks on Livre de Luxe and June Wayne on the history of Tamarind, 1967 March (Box 119, Folder 3)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 3 3/4 IPS in cardboard box. Side 1 holds the Mario Avati discussion. Side 2 is June Wayne continuing her discussion of the history of Tamarind (see also folder 8 in this box).
    - June Wayne on the history of Tamarind Workshop, 1967 March 31 (Box 119, Folder 4)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 3 3/4 IPS in cardboard box. Part 4 of her discussion on the history of Tamarind.
    - June Wayne on the history of Tamarind Workshop, 1967 April 20 (Box 119, Folder 5)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 3 3/4 IPS in cardboard box. Part 5 of her discussion on the history of Tamarind. Note on box indicates the reel may have been recorded at the incorrect speed.
    - Serge Lozingot "Litho, Line and Water", 1967 December 5 (Box 119, Folder 6)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 3 3/4 IPS in cardboard box. Note on back of box indicates much of the tape is empty. June Wayne "Reflections on Jules Langsner" was originally recorded on this reel but may have been erased or damaged.
    - Discussion of lithography and etchings between June Wayne and Mary Lou Baskett, circa 1968 (Box 119, Folder 7)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 7 1/2 IPS in cardboard box. 4 tracks discussing various printmaking projects.
    - Discussion between June Wayne and Mary Lou Baskett, 1968 July 22 (Box 119, Folder 8)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel. 4 tracks discussing Wayne's biography, the formation of Tamarind Workshop and its earlier years.
    - Discussion between June Wayne and Mary Lou Baskett, 1968 July 25-26 (Box 119, Folder 9)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 7 1/2 IPS in cardboard box. 2 tracks discussing paintings and prints including Dreamers, Sanctified, The Cavern, Mushroom People, To get to the Other Side, Strange Moon, At Last a Thousand, The Climb, The Promenade, and Stone Circle. Second track labeled side 4 is 3 3/4 IPS.
    - Discussion between June Wayne and Mary Lou Baskett, 1968 July 26 (Box 120, Folder 1)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 7 1/2 IPS in cardboard box. 2 tracks discussing prints, prints to be destroyed, and drawings.
    - Discussion between June Wayne and Mary Lou Baskett, 1968 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Discussion of various topics, 1968 August 9 (Box 120, Folder 3)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 7 1/2 IPS in cardboard box. 2 tracks taped on track 1 and 4. Discussion covers the topics of Tolkien, Kohens, Cuevas and Kafka, Don Bear, Gary, Indiana; advice on biography, photographs, Pollock, Jules, and Bear.
    - Interview with June Wayne by Molly Briendel, 1969 February 27 (Box 120, Folder 4)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 5" reel. Briendel was the correspondent for Art in Australia magazine. Discussion covers topics of the curatorial aspects of the Tamarind Workshop and the role of curation within the printmaking process.
    - June Wayne on the history of Tamarind Workshop, 1969 April (Box 120, Folder 5)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 1 7/8 IPS in cardboard box.
    - The Museum Curator vis-a-vis the Artist, 1969 May 28 (Box 120, Folder 6)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 7 1/2 IPS in cardboard box. Discussion between June Wayne and Maurice Tuchman. Produced by Claire Loeb and taped at Tamarind.
    - KPFK -- Claire Loeb interviews on the opening of the Pasadena Museum, 1969 December 3 (Box 120, Folder 7)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 1 7/8 IPS in cardboard box. Those included on the reel are June Wayne, Ed Ruscha, Ron Davis, John Coplans, Terbell.
    - KPFK -- "The Sour Apple Tree", 1969 December 10 (Box 120, Folder 8)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel in cardboard box. Those included on the reel are June Wayne, Paul Brach, Nick Wilder.
    - Economic Conference, 1970 January 15 (Box 120, Folder 9)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 1 7/8 IPS in cardboard box. Reel includes the voices of June Wayne, Christman, Faine, Granfield, Goodman, Adams, and MacWhitney.
    - June Wayne speaking at the Iowa University Museum (part 1), 1970 January (Box 121, Folder 1)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 7 1/2 IPS in cardboard box. This portion of the speech covers the topics of Tamarind Workshop history and the general art climate.
    - June Wayne speaking at the Iowa University Museum (part 2), 1970 January (Box 121, Folder 2)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 7 1/2 IPS in cardboard box. This portion of the speech covers the topics of the museum and the art market conditions.
    - Discussion, 1971 February 13 (Box 121, Folder 3)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel in cardboard box. Discussion between Claire Loeb, June Wayne, Joyce Kozloff, Nancy Reeves, Moira Roth, Nancy Shapiro and Judy Chicago.
    - Joan of Art Seminar, 1971 October-November (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Joan of Art Seminar, 1971 November (Box 121, Folder 5)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 1 7/8 IPS in cardboard box. Session 5: women artists and business and professional problems of women artists.
    - Joan of Art Seminar, 1971 December (Box 121, Folder 6)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 1 7/8 IPS in cardboard box. June Wayne speaks on the subject of selling works of art.
    - Joan of Art Seminar, 1972 April-August (Box 121, Folder 7)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 1 7/8 IPS in cardboard box. Side 1: Gilah Hirsch and Judy Elgart on the artist's environment and vocabulary. Side 2: discussion of budgets.
    - Joan of Art Seminar, 1972 April-August (Box 121, Folder 8)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 1 7/8 IPS in cardboard box.Side 1: Bruria Finkel on budgets. Side 2: June Wayne and Harriet Zeitlin on the artist and the collector.
    - Joan of Art Seminar, 1972 April 28 (Box 121, Folder 9)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 1 7/8 IPS in cardboard box. June Wayne on the needs of artist.
    - Joan of Art Seminar, 1972 May (Box 122, Folder 1)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 1 7/8 IPS in cardboard box. Side 1: May 12 Randy Sandel lecture about the artist making a sale. Side 2: May 19 June Wayne lecture on museums.
    - Joan of Art Seminar, 1972 July-August (Box 122, Folder 2)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 1 7/8 IPS in cardboard box. Side 1: July 27 June Wayne, Rachel Rosenthal, and Claudia Champline on roles and vocabulary. Side 2: August 3 Mary Fish and Donna Hanna on budgets.
    - Joan of Art Seminar, 1972 August 17 (Box 122, Folder 3)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 1 7/8 IPS in cardboard box. Side 1: August 17 June Wayne lectures on taxes and law. Side 2: Anita Klebanoff and June Wayne lecture on artist and dealer relationships.
    - Women in the Arts at the University of Wisconsin, Milwaukee, 1972 October 10 (Box 122, Folder 4)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 3 3/4 IPS in cardboard box. June Wayne speaking during the event.
    - Women artists series at Tamarind Studio, 1972 November 12 (Box 122, Folder 5)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel in cardboard box. June Wayne speaking on the professional problems of women artists.
    - KPFK -- June Wayne interviewed by Bruria Finkel, 1973 November (Box 122, Folder 6)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel in cardboard box.
    - Muckenthaler Center -- Fullerton, California, 1974 January (Box 122, Folder 7)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel in cardboard box. June Wayne lecture in conjunction with the exhibition, June Wayne: An Exhibition of Lithographs and Tapestries.
    - Mini Seminars -- Chicago, Illinois, 1975 October 6-7 (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Mini Seminars -- Chicago, Illinois, 1975 October 6-7 (Box 122, Folder 9)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel in cardboard box. June Wayne in Artemisia seminar.
    - WFMT Chicago -- June Wayne interviewed by Studs Terkel, 1975 October 9 (Box 123, Folder 1)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 7 1/2 IPS in cardboard box.
    - Matsumi Kanemitsu interviewed by June Wayne, 1978 December 26 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Matsumi Kanemitsu interviewed June Wayne, 1978 December 27 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Small Reels -- June Wayne and Mary Lou Baskett on Chase and Elements, 1968 May 2 (Box 123, Folder 4)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 4" reel 1 7/8 IPS in cardboard box.
    - Small Reels -- June Wayne on her technique, motivation, and symbols, 1968 July 21 (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Small Reels -- June Wayne on various subjects, 1968 July 21 (Box 123, Folder 6)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 4" reel 1 7/8 IPS in cardboard box. Topics covered in the audio recording are the use of optics in her art, modular systems, and various works of art.
    - Small Reels -- June Wayne to Mary Lou Baskett, 1968 August 3 (Box 123, Folder 7)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 4" reel 7 1/2" IPS in cardboard box. Wayne discusses space constructions of the 1940s.
    - Small Reels -- Mary Lou Baskett to June Wayne, 1968 August 18-19 (Box 123, Folder 8)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 4" reel 3 3/4 IPS in cardboard box. Baskett discusses various topics covering city hall, Franz Alexander, transitions between optics, and Kafka.
    - Small Reels -- June Wayne speaking at the University of New Mexico, 1968 March 23 (Box 123, Folder 9)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 5" reel. Lecture given in conjunction with a solo exhibition at the University of New Mexico Art Museum in Albuquerque.
    - Small Reels -- Museum of Modern Art show and Sterling seminar and Tamarind Workshop staff meeting, 1969 June 4 (Box 123, Folder 10)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 5" reel 3 3/4 IPS.
    - Small Reels -- Museum of Modern Art show and Sterling seminar and report to Tamarind Workshop staff, 1969 June 4 (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Small Reels -- June Wayne interviewed by Sherrie Brandenstein, KNPR-FM Las Vegas, 1981 December 2 (Box 123, Folder 12)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 5" reel 7 1/2" IPS. Interview topic is on the Dorothy Series.
    - De Kooning Documentary, 1969 August 29 (Box 123, Folder 13)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel. Includes reactions to the DeKooning exhibition at the Los Angeles County Museum of Art with KFPK interviewer, Claire Loeb.
    - De Kooning Documentary, 1969 August 29 (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - De Kooning Documentary, 1969 August 29 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Tamarind Workshop -- Call Goodman lecture at the California Institute of the Arts, 1967 August 1 (Box 124, Folder 2)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 5" reel 3 3/4 IPS in cardboard box. Topics covered in the audio recording are aspects of business operation and selling.
    - Tamarind Workshop -- Board Meeting, 1967 November 27 (Box 124, Folder 3)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 7 1/2 IPS in cardboard box. Board meeting was on the topic of Hank Baum and insurance.
    - Tamarind Workshop -- KFPK Broadcast (part 1), 1969 July 3 (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Tamarind Workshop -- KFPK Broadcast (part 2), 1969 July 3 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Tamarind Workshop -- KFPK Broadcast (part 3), 1969 July 3 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Tamarind Workshop -- KFPK Broadcast (part 4), 1969 July 3 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Tamarind Workshop -- KPFK Broadcast, "Arts and Artists", 1960 July 18 (Box 124, Folder 8)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 7 1/2 IPS in cardboard box. Voices included on the audio tape are Henry Seldis, June Wayne, Clinton Adams.
    - You and Modern Art -- Program #3, 1953 (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - You and Modern Art -- Program #5, 1953 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - You and Modern Art -- Program #6, recorded in Torrance, CA, 1953 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - You and Modern Art -- Program #6, Los Angeles Group, 1953 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - You and Modern Art -- Program #7, 1953 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - You and Modern Art -- Program #8, Expressionism, 1953 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - You and Modern Art -- Program #9, 1953 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - You and Modern Art -- Organizational Meeting, 1953 (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - You and Modern Art -- Surrealism, 1953 (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - You and Modern Art -- Architecture, 1954 (Box 125, Folder 9)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 3 3/4 IPS in cardboard box. Features Clinton Adams.
    - You and Modern Art -- Impressionism and Post-Impressionism, 1954 (Box 126, Folder 1)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 3 3/4 IPS in cardboard box. Features Fred Reid and June Wayne reading Reid's poetry. Also features Doug McClelland.
    - You and Modern Art -- Program #6, 1954 March (Box 126, Folder 2)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 3 3/4 IPS in cardboard box. Features Doug McClelland.
    - You and Modern Art -- Jules Langsner, City Hall, and Bill Stout, 1955 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Four Stone -- Tape 4: Lithography, Gene Sturman and Serge Lozingot, circa 1969 (Box 190, Folder 1)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 5" reel 3 3/4 IPS. Gene Sturman and Serge Lozingot etching, wet wash, inking, rolling, and fanning.
    - Four Stones -- Terry Sanders and Serge Lozingot, circa 1969 (Box 190, Folder 2)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 5" reel 1 7/8 IPS.
    - Four Stones, circa 1969 (Box 190, Folder 3)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 5" reel 1 7/8 IPS. Features Serge Lozingot and Mike.
    - Four Stones, circa 1969 (Box 190, Folder 4)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 5" reel 1 7/8 IPS. Features Gene Sturman.
    - Four Stones, circa 1969 (Box 190, Folder 5)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 5" reel 3 3/4 IPS. Features Serge Lozingot and Mike.
    - Four Stones, circa 1969 (Box 190, Folder 6)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 5" reel 1 7/8 IPS. Features Serge Lozingot and others.
    - Four Stones, circa 1969 (Box 190, Folder 7)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 5" reel 3 3/4 IPS. Manufacturer: Audiotape.
    - Four Stones, circa 1969 (Box 190, Folder 8)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 5" reel 3 3/4 IPS. There are notes included with this reel, indicating dates of recording, and Alex Van der Kar's voice; see folder entitled YRLSC_562_190_8 in this box.
    - Four Stones, circa 1969 (Box 190, Folder 9)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 5" reel 3 3/4 IPS. Duplicate of Reel A-15. Includes camera roll 49.
    - Zubin Mehta Film, circa 1968 (Box 190, Folder 10)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 5" reel. Manufacturer: Scotch. Included on the reel are the Rubenstein rehearsal, and audio from the dressing room with Zubin Mehta, various musicians (the violinist, bassonist, and the clarinet player), and musicians in the lounge.
    - Zubin Mehta Film -- Music #1, circa 1968 (Box 190, Folder 11)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 5" reel. Manufacturer: Audiotape. Music #1. There are notes included with this reel; see folder entitled YRLSC_562_190_11 in this box. Features Terry Sanders.
    - Zubin Mehta Film -- Music Film #1, 1968 October 24 (Box 190, Folder 12)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 5" reel. Manufacturer: Scotch. Music Film #1. There are notes included with this reel, indicating Terry Sanders speaking at the start of the film; see folder entitled YRLSC_562_190_12 in this box.
    - Cal Goodman Lecture, 1967 April 12 (Box 190, Folder 13)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 5" reel 3 3/4 IPS. Manufacturer: Scotch. Duplicate copy. Lecture on contracts, the structure of contracts, and a review of the course. There are notes included with this reel, indicating the tape as evidence of Cal Goodman's professional position and relationship with Wayne; see folder entitled YRLSC_562_190_13 in this box.
    - Four Stones, 1977 May (Box 191, Folder 1)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 7 1/2 IPS. Made at Glen Gleem. Taken directly from film soundtrack of Wayne's own print. Note on the box indicates that it is the full track and that there is no sync. Included with this reel is a sound report; see folder entitled YRLSC_562_191_1 in this box.
    - Lithograph, 1977 May 9 (Box 191, Folder 2)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 7 1/2 IPS. Taken at Glen Gleem from track provided by Terry Sanders as representing Homage to a Lithograph. Note on the box indicates that there are 3 reels and that there is no sync.
    - Zubin Mehta Film -- Performance of Brahms in Ojai, California, 1969 May 25 (Box 191, Folder 3)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 7 1/2 IPS. Music #1. Nagra-Éclair Symphony. Included with this reel is a note indicating that the reel is music only; see folder entitled YRLSC_562_191_3 in this box. Scanned by Wayne July 1, 1974.
    - Yankee Transcendoodle, by Joseph Byrd, 1969 May 25 (Box 191, Folder 4)
      1 - 1/4" audio tape on 7" reel 7 1/2 IPS. Included with this reel is the track listing on Side One and Side Two; see folder entitled YRLSC_562_191_4 in this box. Note on box indicates 1/4 TK. Reproduced by Peter Kirby on April 11, 2001.
    - The Dorothy Series, undated (Box 131, Folder 13)
      Scope and Contents
      Audio tracks.
  - Subseries 2: Cassettes, 1956-1982
    This subseries includes recordings of interviews, speeches and presentations, and panel discussions with Wayne at such venues as university convocations, professional conferences and symposia, museum and gallery openings, and radio shows.
    - June Wayne interviewed by E. Gunter Troche, 1958 August 8 (Box 126, Folder 4)
      28 minutes. 2 audio cassettes. Copy of reel-to-reel audio box 1, folder 1. 2 copies.
    - KNX Kaleidoscope: June Wayne on Tamarind, 1965 September 3 (Box 126, Folder 5)
      1 audio cassette. Hosted by Fred Anderson.
    - Jules Langsner funeral services, 1967 (Box 126, Folder 6)
      1 audio cassette. Voices in order of appearance: Bill Brices, Henry Seldis, Ken Ross, Lillian Weiner, Jessie Reichek, Fred Wight, Gifford Phillips, Stanley Fleishman, Sam Francis, Rita Morrison, Henry Hopkins, Tom Leavitt, June Wayne, Lerser Feitelson, Peter Selz, Rudd Brown, Clement Greenberg, John Entenza, Phil Gaston, and Don Brewer.
    - June Wayne lecture at College Art Association, 1973 January (Box 126, Folder 7)
      1 audio cassette.
    - June Wayne speaks about Anni Albers, circa 1970 (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - June Wayne lecture at Palomar, 1976 March 15 (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - June Wayne interviewed by Virginia Rubin, 1976 November 22 (Box 126, Folder 10)
      1 audio cassette. See also Rubin paper.
    - June Wayne interviewed by Louise Lewis, 1976 December 7 (Box 126, Folder 11)
      1 audio cassette. Marked as "corrections on Lesser interview."
    - KCET: 28 Tonight -- Artists' Residual Rights Law (AB 1391), 1977 January 20 (Box 126, Folder 12)
      1 audio cassette. Guests include June Wayne, Albert Elsen, and Alan Sieroty. Moderated by Susan Freedman.
    - Art Library Society of North America -- Beyond Illustration: Livres D'Artiste of the 20th Century, 1977 February 3 (Box 126, Folder 13)
      2 audio cassettes. Parts 1 and 2. Panel discussion moderated by Mel Edelstein and featuring June Wayne, Breon Mitchell, and Clarice Davis.
    - June Wayne interviewed by Bill Bragg, 1978 July 24 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Interview with Matsumi Kanemitsu and opening at Claremont, 1978 (Box 127, Folder 2)
      1 audio cassette. Cassette contains two recordings: a discussion between June Wayne and Matsumi Kanemitsu (7/24/1978) and the opening of the exhibition, June Wayne: Paintings, Tapestries and Lithographs at the Montgomery Gallery of Pomona College (11/5/1978).
    - June Wayne: Tapisseries, Lithographies opening at the Foundation Pescatore, Luxembourg, 1979 January 15 (Box 127, Folder 3)
      1 audio cassette. Speech by Jeanine Dubois.
    - June Wayne interviewed by Nancy Devor, 1979 April 19 (Box 127, Folder 4)
      1 audio cassette. For "Taxing Times".
    - June Wayne interviewed by Isabel Anderson, 1980 February 12 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - NPR -- The Sunday Show: June Wayne, 1982 (Box 127, Folder 6)
      1 audio cassette. Interviewed by M. Christianson.
    - San Diego Public Radio: June Wayne and Carla Seaquist, 1982 January 7 (Box 127, Folder 7)
      1 audio cassette. Cassette includes 5 interviews.
    - University of Alabama: June Wayne lecture and interview, 1982 October 6 (Box 127, Folder 8)
      1 audio cassette. Includes 2 segments during visits to the University of Alabama: June Wayne speaking and an interview with Carol Sokol.
    - June Wayne interviewed by Carol Sokol in Birmingham, Alabama, 1982 October 6 (Box 127, Folder 9)
      1 audio cassette. Interview on the occasion of the opening of June Wayne: Dorothy Series at the University of Alabama, Birmingham.
    - Tamarind: A 25-Year Retrospective (part 1), 1984 December 2 (Box 127, Folder 10)
      2 audio cassettes. 2 copies of tape 1.